The History of Love is a drama, romance, war film directed by Radu Mihăileanu.
The story of a long-lost book that mysteriously reappears and connects an old man
searching for his son with a girl seeking a cure for her mother's loneliness.
Leopold Gursky, played by Derek Jacobi.
Alma Singer, played by Sophie Nélisse.
Alma Mereminski, played by Gemma Arterton.
Bruno Leibovitch, played by Elliott Gould.
Charlotte Singer, played by Torri Higginson.
Young Leopold Gursky, played by Mark Rendall.
The History of Love is a 2016 internationally co-produced romantic drama film directed by Radu Mihăileanu and
written by Mihăileanu and Marcia Romano, based on the 2005 novel of the same name by Nicole Krauss.
The film stars Derek Jacobi, Sophie Nélisse, Gemma Arterton and Elliott Gould.
The tone is emotional.